{
    "subject": "Jessica_Bennett",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Spike_Lester",
    "human_readable": "Jessica Bennett is married to Spike Lester.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9564469456672668,
            "question": "Is there a known relationship between Jessica Bennett and Spike Lester?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9124031662940979,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the relationship between Jessica Bennett and Spike Lester?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8868947625160217,
            "question": "To whom is Spike Lester married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8851675391197205,
            "question": "Is Spike Lester married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8764379620552063,
            "question": "Name the person married to Jessica Bennett."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8622854948043823,
            "question": "Who is Jessica Bennett married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.860435962677002,
            "question": "Who are Jessica Bennett and Spike Lester?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7745944261550903,
            "question": "Who is Spike Lester's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6208123564720154,
            "question": "What is the marital status of Spike Lester?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5856214761734009,
            "question": "What is the name of Jessica Bennett's spouse?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Jessica Bennett is married to Spike Lester.",
            "html": "yago_30160_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the marital status of Spike Lester?",
            "html": "yago_30160_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Spike Lester's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_30160_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are Jessica Bennett and Spike Lester?",
            "html": "yago_30160_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30160_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30160_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30160_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30160_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30160_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30160_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30160_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30160_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30160_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30160_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information, I can confirm that the triple is indeed supported by the documents.\n\nHere is the structured JSON format response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Spike marries Jessica Bennett (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_30160/re-ranker-msmarco/65.txt) and they live together in the Bennett family home after their marriage (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_30160/re-ranker-msmarco/21.txt). This confirms that Jessica Bennett is indeed married to Spike Lester."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly indicate that Jessica Bennett was married to Herbert \"Spike\" Lester, which supports the statement that Jessica Bennett is married to Spike Lester."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}